class English {
  static const List<Map<String, dynamic>> fourthMastery = [
    {
      'answer': 'Voice of verbs',
      'question':
          'indicates the form of transitive verb that shows whether the subject is the doer or the receiver of the action',
    },
    {
      'answer': 'Active voice',
      'question': 'shows the subject as the doer of the action',
    },
    {
      'answer': 'Passive voice',
      'question': 'shows the receiver of the action as the subject',
    },
    {
      'answer': 'Process',
      'question':
          'the paragraph of explaining a process is a type of development telling how something is done or how it should be done',
    },
    {
      'answer': 'Incidents',
      'question': 'illustrate your main point by narrating the event',
    },
    {'answer': 'Definition', 'question': 'identifies the term'},
    {
      'answer': 'Comparison',
      'question':
          'shows the similarities between two or more people, objects, places, things, or ideas',
    },
    {
      'answer': 'Contrast',
      'question':
          'shows the differences between two persons, places, things, or ideas',
    },
    {
      'answer': 'Collocations',
      'question': 'are related words that are combined with a sentence',
    },
    {
      'answer': 'Interview',
      'question':
          'is a meeting between two or more persons for soliciting viewer opinion',
    },
    {
      'answer': 'Autobiography',
      'question':
          'is a form of literary piece that tells a story of one person written by the same person',
    },
    {
      'answer': 'Biography',
      'question':
          "is a literary form of a person's life written by another person",
    },
    {
      'answer': 'Narrative',
      'question':
          'is a story created in a constructive format that describes a sequence of fictional or non-fictional events',
    },
    {'answer': 'Cud', 'question': 'food forced up into the mouth'},
    {'answer': 'Ponder', 'question': 'examine, consider carefully'},
    {'answer': 'Bolted', 'question': 'moved or sprung suddenly'},
    {
      'answer': 'Ogre',
      'question':
          'a person who is felt to be particularly cruel, brutish or hideous',
    },
    {
      'answer': 'Gorge',
      'question': 'a deep narrow passage with a steep rocky side',
    },
    {
      'answer': 'Local color',
      'question': 'It uses a regional future in an artistic work',
    },
    {
      'answer': 'Direct speech',
      'question': 'is the exact word or words of the speaker',
    },
    {
      'answer': 'Indirect speech',
      'question':
          'is the reported speech by another person about the direct speech of the speaker',
    },
    {
      'answer': 'Anecdote',
      'question': "a brief account of a true event in someone's life",
    },
    {
      'answer': 'Proposition',
      'question': 'two teams discuss a topic referred to as proposition',
    },
    {
      'answer': 'Affirmative team',
      'question': 'maintains the acceptance of the proposition',
    },
    {'answer': 'Negative team', 'question': 'Disputes it'},
    {
      'answer': 'Derivational words',
      'question':
          'it means that the word are derived or taken from the origin of the words',
    },
  ];
  static const List<Map<String, dynamic>> thirdPeriodical =
      <Map<String, dynamic>>[
    <String, String>{
      'answer': 'Adolescence',
      'question': 'a period of change, development, and growth.',
    },
    <String, String>{
      'answer': 'rustled',
      'question': 'made a soft, light sound.',
    },
    <String, String>{
      'answer': 'hovered',
      'question': 'moved to and from near a place.',
    },
    <String, String>{
      'answer': 'perched',
      'question': 'rested or sat on something.',
    },
    <String, String>{
      'answer': 'choked',
      'question': 'suffocated or become unable to breathe.',
    },
    <String, String>{
      'answer': 'driftwood',
      'question':
          'wood that is floating in water or carried to the shore by water.',
    },
    <String, String>{
      'answer': 'Simple sentence',
      'question': 'is composed of one independent or principal or main clause.',
    },
    <String, String>{
      'answer': 'Compound sentence',
      'question':
          'has two independent clauses connected by AND, OR, BUT, SO, and NOR, FOR, or a conjunctive advert MOREOVER, FURTHERMORE, NEVERTHELESS, CONSEQUENTLY, HOWEVER, or punctuation mark.',
    },
    <String, String>{
      'answer': 'Complex sentence',
      'question':
          'consists of one or more subordinate clauses or two independent clauses.',
    },
    <String, String>{
      'answer': 'Compound complex sentence',
      'question':
          'consists of two independent clauses and one or more subordinate complexes.',
    },
    <String, String>{
      'answer': 'irony',
      'question':
          'is a figure of speech that states the opposite idea of what is meant.',
    },
    <String, String>{
      'answer': 'oxymoron',
      'question': 'contradicting terms that appear side by side.',
    },
    <String, String>{
      'answer': 'paradox',
      'question': 'is a statement that appears to contrast itself.',
    },
    <String, String>{
      'answer': 'Intonation',
      'question': 'is the variation of pitch while speaking.',
    },
    <String, String>{
      'answer': 'Pitch',
      'question': 'refers to the way your voice goes up and down.',
    },
    <String, String>{
      'answer': 'rising intonation',
      'question': 'is used in questions answerable by yes or no.',
    },
    <String, String>{
      'answer': 'falling intonation',
      'question': 'is used in questions that cannot be answered by yes or no.',
    },
    <String, String>{
      'answer': 'stress',
      'question':
          'is the relative emphasis that may be given to certain syllables in a word or to certain words in a phrase or sentence.',
    },
    <String, String>{
      'answer': 'Print materials',
      'question':
          'are books, newspapers, magazines, brochures, pamphlets, and periodicals.',
    },
    <String, String>{
      'answer': 'Non-print resources',
      'question': 'can be audio and visual.',
    },
    <String, String>{
      'answer': 'Newspaper',
      'question':
          'is a daily publication issued for general circulation which contains news of informative articles, current events, advertisements, and others.',
    },
    <String, String>{
      'answer': 'raising questions',
      'question': 'means asking or requesting for information or action.',
    },
    <String, String>{
      'answer': 'closed questions',
      'question': 'demand a yes/no, true/false or right/wrong.',
    },
    <String, String>{
      'answer': 'open questions',
      'question':
          'leave room for a description or opinion, and are more useful in eliciting information.',
    },
    <String, String>{
      'answer': 'Jose M. Hernandez',
      'question':
          'describes this period as a time of self-discovery and of rapid growth.',
    },
    <String, String>{
      'answer': 'His Native Soil',
      'question': 'won the first Commonwealth Literary Award in 1940.',
    },
    <String, String>{
      'answer': 'love',
      'question': 'a strong tender affection.',
    },
    <String, String>{'answer': 'rare', 'question': 'occurring infrequently.'},
    <String, String>{
      'answer': 'persistent',
      'question': 'continuing to exist.',
    },
    <String, String>{
      'answer': 'groan',
      'question': 'to utter the sound of pain.',
    },
    <String, String>{'answer': 'plead', 'question': 'to ask, beg, beseech.'},
    <String, String>{
      'answer': 'connector or conjunction',
      'question': 'a word that joins words, phrases, clauses, or sentences.',
    },
    <String, String>{
      'answer': 'Coordinating Conjunctions',
      'question':
          'these conjunctions connect words or group words of equal rank.',
    },
    <String, String>{
      'answer': 'Correlative Conjunctions',
      'question': 'these conjunctions are used in pairs.',
    },
    <String, String>{
      'answer': 'Subordinating Conjunctions',
      'question':
          'these conjunctions denote reason, condition, concession, time, place, purpose, and result.',
    },
    <String, String>{
      'answer': 'Miscommunication',
      'question': 'is the result of poor listening skill.',
    },
    <String, String>{
      'answer': 'Figurative language',
      'question': 'is used to create intense pictures.',
    },
    <String, String>{
      'answer': 'Simile',
      'question': 'is the direct comparison of two different things.',
    },
    <String, String>{
      'answer': 'Metaphor',
      'question': 'is an implied comparison.',
    },
    <String, String>{
      'answer': 'anecdote',
      'question':
          'is a kind of literature that pertains to a short narrative text of interesting and entertaining events.',
    }
  ];
  static const List<Map<String, dynamic>> thirdMonthly = <Map<String, dynamic>>[
    <String, String>{
      'answer': 'reproduction',
      'question': 'the means of all organisms to make new organisms.',
    },
    <String, String>{
      'answer': 'gametes',
      'question':
          'reproductive cells that contain half the number of chromosomes.',
    },
    <String, String>{
      'answer': 'chromosomes',
      'question':
          'carry the information that decides how the organisms will look a like.',
    },
    <String, String>{
      'answer': 'chromosomes',
      'question': 'the nuclei of the two cells, together with this, unite.',
    },
    <String, String>{
      'answer': 'genes',
      'question':
          'provide the instructions and control the manifestation of traits.',
    },
    <String, String>{
      'answer': 'fertilization',
      'question': 'the union of male and female.',
    },
    <String, String>{
      'answer': 'fertilization',
      'question': 'is possible when a male gamete meets with a female gamete.',
    },
    <String, String>{'answer': 'egg', 'question': 'female gamete'},
    <String, String>{'answer': 'sperm', 'question': 'male gamete'},
    <String, String>{
      'answer': 'zygote',
      'question': 'results when two cells unite.',
    },
    <String, String>{
      'answer': 'internal fertilization',
      'question': 'occurs within the reproductive system.',
    },
    <String, String>{
      'answer': 'penis',
      'question': 'responsible for the transfer of sperm cells.',
    },
    <String, String>{
      'answer': 'copulation',
      'question':
          'the transfer of male gamete into the female reproductive system.',
    },
    <String, String>{
      'answer': 'external fertilization',
      'question': 'occurs in the outside environment.',
    },
    <String, String>{
      'answer': 'sex organs',
      'question': 'responsible for the formation of gametes.',
    },
    <String, String>{
      'answer': 'dioecious',
      'question': 'organisms that may either be male or female.',
    },
    <String, String>{
      'answer': 'monoecious or hermaphroditic',
      'question': 'means two houses in the Greek word.',
    },
    <String, String>{
      'answer': 'monoecious or hermaphroditic',
      'question':
          'organisms that have both male and female reproductive systems.',
    },
    <String, String>{
      'answer': 'protogyny',
      'question': 'the ability to switch or change sex.',
    },
    <String, String>{
      'answer': 'protandry',
      'question': 'when the sperms are produced before the egg.',
    },
    <String, String>{
      'answer': 'protogyny',
      'question': 'when the egg cells are produced before the sperm cells.',
    },
    <String, String>{
      'answer': 'stamen',
      'question': 'the male part of the flower.',
    },
    <String, String>{
      'answer': 'stamen',
      'question': 'the reproductive structure in the plants.',
    },
    <String, String>{
      'answer': 'carpel',
      'question': 'the female part of the flower.',
    },
    <String, String>{'answer': 'pollen', 'question': 'the male gametophyte.'},
    <String, String>{'answer': 'ovule', 'question': 'the female gametophyte.'},
    <String, String>{
      'answer': 'fallopian tube',
      'question':
          'female reproductive system organ where the union of the egg and sperm occurs.',
    },
    <String, String>{
      'answer': 'sperm cell',
      'question': 'penetrates once the sperm cells reach the matured egg.',
    }
  ];
}
